

Ana Lastoviria

Guest Service Agent

Friendly and experienced Guest Service Agent and Receptionist. Reliable, tech-savvy attentive to detail. Full work rights in Australia, current RSA, WWCC, own transport. Looking forward to creating the most memorable experiences of Melbourne for the guests of your business!

a.lastovirya@gmail.com

0404207477

Brunswick West

in linkedin.com/in/ana-lastoviria

WORK EXPERIENCE

Guest Service Agent / Receptionist Pegasus Apart'Hotel

07/2019 - 03/2020

Melbourne, VIC

Tasks

- Working in a team of ~12-15 people, doing 80-100 of each check-ins and check-outs per day in a property of ~285 rooms;
- Operating busy switchboard, emails, mail distribution;
- Reservations, data entry;
- Following admin checklist, complying with hotel procedures and
- Taking care of the workspace: keeping it tidy, clutter-free and organized. Keeping track of and stocking amenities.

Teacher

Vox Singing Academy

01/2019 - 01/2020

Melbourne, VIC

Achievements/Tasks

- Providing high-quality teaching one to one and in groups;
- · Making customers feel welcome and relaxed, inspiring and energizing them;
- Self-managing, scheduling and administration (CRM);
- Excellent feedback from customers, ~ 80% retention rate.

Guest Service Agent / Receptionist Adara St Kilda (former Apartments Ink)

08/2017 - 06/2019

St Kilda, VIC

Achievements/Tasks

- Reception duties: check-in, check-out, reservations, phones, emails;
- · Admin duties: shift logs, keys and parking audit, night audit;
- o Office/building management duties: basic maintenance of the rooms and facilities, liaising with the body corporate, troubleshooting when alone on duty;
- Onsite nightly duty, handling emergency phone line.

Educational Travel Agent Anima Project Study & Travel

11/2012 - 11/2016

Moscow, Russia

Achievements/Tasks

- Client management from scratch, managing ~10 clients simultaneously, individuals and groups;
- Visa support, travel bookings;
- Scheduling, prioritizing tasks, time management;
- Representing the company at international workshops and conferences, networking with partners;
- Light marketing duties: preparation of marketing materials, website content management (Bitrix), social media engagement.

SKILLS & QUALITIES

Customer service

Reception

Switchboard

Microsoft Office

Mac Applications

Communication

Data entry

Team work

Adaptability

Prioritising

Problem solving

Initiative

Work Under Pressure

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Casual shelter attendant Rabbit Runaway Orphanage

2018 - 2019

Tasks/Achievements

• Cleaning and all-round tasks at the shelter.

All-rounder Irish Film Festival

2017 - 2018

Tasks/Achievements

- Postering;
- Greeting and information support to guests;
- · General all-rounding at the screenings.

Front gates all-rounder Laneway Festival Melbourne

2017

Tasks/Achievements

- Wristbanding;
- Providing customer service and information at the front gates.

EDUCATION

Advanced Diploma in Music Melbourne Polytechnic

2017 - 2018

LANGUAGES

English

Full Professional Proficiency

Russian

Native or Bilingual Proficiency